RG 062:169, Town of Woodstock
Connecticut State Library
Town of Woodstock records
1843-1927
Connecticut State Library
Woodstock (Conn.)
17.25 cubic feet
Administrative, election, land, military and tax records for the town of Woodstock.
RG062_169
T000594
Historical Note
The town of Woodstock was settled in 1686 as New Roxbury. The name changed in March 1690 to Woodstock. It was annexed to Connecticut in May 1749.
Scope and Content
Administrative, election, land, military and tax records for the town of Woodstock.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Elections -- Connecticut -- Woodstock -- Statistics; Voting -- Connecticut -- Woodstock -- Statistics; Soldiers -- Connecticut -- Woodstock; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Woodstock; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Woodstock -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Woodstock -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Woodstock -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Woodstock -- Registers; Deeds -- Connecticut -- Woodstock
Places:
Woodstock (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1843-1927
  - Appointments of administrators (Box Box 1)
  - Bills paid, 1921-1922 (Box Box 1)
  - Bills paid, 1923-1924 (Box Box 2)
  - Bills paid, 1925-1927 (Box Box 3)
  - Bonds (Box Box 4)
  - Deeds (Box Box 4)
  - Election returns (Box Box 5)
  - Military enrollment lists (Box Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box Box 6)
  - Voting lists (Box Box 6)
  - Assessor's books, 1843, 1853 (Box Box 6)
  - Individual tax lists, 1926 (Box Box 6)
  - Tax abstracts
    Box 7 is on oversize shelving.
    - North, 1852 (Box Box 7)
    - South, 1852 (Box Box 7)
    - North, 1853 (Box Box 7)
    - South, 1853 (Box Box 7)
    - West, 1853 (Box Box 7)
    - North, 1854 (Box Box 7)
    - South, 1854 (Box Box 7)
    - West, 1854 (Box Box 7)
    - South, 1855 (Box Box 7)
    - West, 1855 (Box Box 7)
    - North, 1856 (Box Box 8)
    - South, 1856 (Box Box 8)
    - West, 1856 (Box Box 8)
    - North and East, 1857 (Box Box 8)
    - South, 1857 (Box Box 8)
    - West, 1857 (Box Box 8)
    - North and East, 1858 (Box Box 8)
    - South, 1858 (Box Box 8)
    - West, 1858 (Box Box 8)
    - North and East, 1859 (Box Box 8)
    - South, 1859 (Box Box 8)
    - West, 1859 (Box Box 8)
    - North and East, 1860 (Box Box 9)
    - South, 1860 (Box Box 9)
    - West, 1860 (Box Box 9)
    - North and East, 1861 (Box Box 9)
    - South, 1861 (Box Box 9)
    - West, 1861 (Box Box 9)
    - North and East, 1862 (Box Box 9)
    - South, 1862 (Box Box 9)
    - West, 1862 (Box Box 9)
    - North and East, 1863 (Box Box 9)
    - South, 1863 (Box Box 9)
    - West, 1863 (Box Box 9)
    - North, 1864 (Box Box 10)
    - South, 1864 (Box Box 10)
    - West, 1864 (Box Box 10)
    - North, 1865 (Box Box 10)
    - South, 1865 (Box Box 10)
    - West, 1865 (Box Box 10)
    - North and East, 1866 (Box Box 10)
    - South, 1866 (Box Box 10)
    - West, 1866 (Box Box 10)
    - North and East, 1867 (Box Box 10)
    - South, 1867 (Box Box 10)
    - West, 1867 (Box Box 10)
    - North and East, 1868 (Box Box 11)
    - South, 1868 (Box Box 11)
    - West, 1868 (Box Box 11)
    - North and East, 1869 (Box Box 11)
    - South, 1869 (Box Box 11)
    - West, 1869 (Box Box 11)
    - North and East, 1870 (Box Box 11)
    - South, 1870 (Box Box 11)
    - West, 1870 (Box Box 11)
    - North, 1871 (Box Box 11)
    - South, 1871 (Box Box 11)
    - West, 1871 (Box Box 11)
    - North, 1872 (Box Box 12)
    - South, 1872 (Box Box 12)
    - West, 1872 (Box Box 12)
    - North, 1873 (Box Box 12)
    - South, 1873 (Box Box 12)
    - West, 1873 (Box Box 12)
    - North, 1874 (Box Box 12)
    - South, 1874 (Box Box 12)
    - West, 1874 (Box Box 12)
    - North, 1875 (Box Box 12)
    - South, 1875 (Box Box 12)
    - West, 1875 (Box Box 12)
    - North, 1876 (Box Box 13)
    - South, 1876 (Box Box 13)
    - West, 1876 (Box Box 13)
    - North, 1877 (Box Box 13)
    - South, 1877 (Box Box 13)
    - West, 1877 (Box Box 13)
    - North, 1878 (Box Box 13)
    - South, 1878 (Box Box 13)
    - West, 1878 (Box Box 13)
    - North, 1879 (Box Box 13)
    - South, 1879 (Box Box 13)
    - West, 1879 (Box Box 13)
    - North, 1880 (Box Box 14)
    - South, 1880 (Box Box 14)
    - West, 1880 (Box Box 14)
    - North, 1881 (Box Box 14)
    - South, 1881 (Box Box 14)
    - West, 1881 (Box Box 14)
    - North, 1882 (Box Box 14)
    - South, 1882 (Box Box 14)
    - West, 1882 (Box Box 14)
    - North, 1883 (Box Box 14)
    - South, 1883 (Box Box 14)
    - West, 1883 (Box Box 14)
    - North, 1884 (Box Box 15)
    - South, 1884 (Box Box 15)
    - West, 1884 (Box Box 15)
    - North, 1885 (Box Box 15)
    - South, 1885 (Box Box 15)
    - West, 1885 (Box Box 15)
    - North, 1886 (Box Box 15)
    - South, 1886 (Box Box 15)
    - West, 1886 (Box Box 15)
    - North, 1887 (Box Box 16)
    - South, 1887 (Box Box 16)
    - West, 1887 (Box Box 16)
    - North, 1888 (Box Box 16)
    - South, 1888 (Box Box 16)
    - West, 1888 (Box Box 16)
    - North and East, 1889 (Box Box 16)
    - South, 1889 (Box Box 16)
    - West, 1889 (Box Box 16)
    - North, 1890 (Box Box 17)
    - South, 1890 (Box Box 17)
    - West, 1890 (Box Box 17)
    - North, 1891 (Box Box 17)
    - South, 1891 (Box Box 17)
    - West, 1891 (Box Box 17)
    - North, 1892 (Box Box 17)
    - South, 1892 (Box Box 17)
    - West, 1892 (Box Box 17)
    - North, 1893 (Box Box 18)
    - South, 1893 (Box Box 18)
    - West, 1893 (Box Box 18)
    - North and East, 1894 (Box Box 18)
    - South, 1894 (Box Box 18)
    - West, 1894 (Box Box 18)
    - North and East, 1895 (Box Box 18)
    - South, 1895 (Box Box 18)
    - West, 1895 (Box Box 18)
    - North, 1896 (Box Box 19)
    - South, 1896 (Box Box 19)
    - West, 1896 (Box Box 19)
    - North, 1897 (Box Box 19)
    - South, 1897 (Box Box 19)
    - West, 1897 (Box Box 19)
    - North, 1898 (Box Box 19)
    - South, 1898 (Box Box 19)
    - West, 1898 (Box Box 19)
    - North, 1899 (Box Box 20)
    - South, 1899 (Box Box 20)
    - West, 1899 (Box Box 20)
    - North, 1900 (Box Box 20)
    - South, 1900 (Box Box 20)
    - West, 1900 (Box Box 20)
    - North, 1901 (Box Box 20)
    - South, 1901 (Box Box 20)
    - West, 1901 (Box Box 20)
    - North, 1902 (Box Box 21)
    - South, 1902 (Box Box 21)
    - West, 1902 (Box Box 21)
    - North, 1903 (Box Box 21)
    - South, 1903 (Box Box 21)
    - West, 1903 (Box Box 21)
    - North, 1904 (Box Box 21)
    - South, 1904 (Box Box 21)
    - West, 1904 (Box Box 21)
    - North, 1905 (Box Box 22)
    - South, 1905 (Box Box 22)
    - West, 1905 (Box Box 22)
    - North, 1906 (Box Box 22)
    - South, 1906 (Box Box 22)
    - West, 1906 (Box Box 22)
    - North, 1907 (Box Box 22)
    - South, 1907 (Box Box 22)
    - West, 1907 (Box Box 22)
    - North, 1908 (Box Box 23)
    - South, 1908 (Box Box 23)
    - West, 1908 (Box Box 23)
    - North, 1909 (Box Box 23)
    - South, 1909 (Box Box 23)
    - West, 1909 (Box Box 23)
    - North, 1910 (Box Box 23)
    - South, 1910 (Box Box 23)
    - West, 1910 (Box Box 23)
    - North, 1911 (Box Box 24)
    - South, 1911 (Box Box 24)
    - West, 1911 (Box Box 24)
    - North, 1912 (Box Box 24)
    - South, 1912 (Box Box 24)
    - West, 1912 (Box Box 24)
    - North, 1913 (Box Box 24)
    - South, 1913 (Box Box 24)
    - West, 1913 (Box Box 24)